well this hour we're going to talk about
那么这个小时我们要谈谈
fear and worry fear and worry are
恐惧和担心恐惧和担忧
significant problems that can dominate a
可以支配的重大问题
person's life fear and worry are
人的生命恐惧和忧虑
complicated problems we're going to talk
我们要谈的复杂问题
about the problems of fear and worry and
关于恐惧和担忧的问题
then we're gonna also talk in detail
然后我们也会详细谈谈
about the biblical solutions to fear and
关于恐惧和恐惧的圣经解决方案
worry we'll also have some examples of
担心我们也会有一些例子
actual counseling cases of fear and
实际的恐惧和咨询案例
worry as well fear and worry are complex
担心以及恐惧和担忧都很复杂
issues why do I say that well this is
问题为什么我说，嗯，这是
true because I might have four men come
是的，因为我可能有四个人来
to me with really the same problem
对我来说真的是同样的问题
they're all out of work none of them can
他们都没有工作，他们都无法做到
find a job and they're all worried about
找工作和他们都担心
that they're presenting problem is I'm
他们提出的问题是我
worried about when will I find a job
担心我什么时候能找到工作
will I find a job but then each of the
我会找到一份工作，但随后各
four has a different twist to that
四个有不同的转折
presenting problem one of you one of
提出你们其中一个问题
them is calling you for help with
他们正在打电话给你寻求帮助
depression the second guy is asking for
抑郁症是第二个人要求的
help with anger the third guy he wants
帮助愤怒他想要的第三个人
marriage help because he and his wife
婚姻帮助因为他和他的妻子
were arguing a lot right now and the
现在正在争论很多
fourth guy wonders why he is suddenly
第四个人想知道他为什么突然
unable to have relations with his wife
无法与妻子建立关系
well then when we dig deeper we find
那么当我们深入挖掘时，我们会发现
more complexities with these four
这四个更复杂
out-of-work guys the depressed man
失业的男人，失业的男人
hasn't left his house in two weeks
两周后他还没有离开他的家
because of shame the angry man blames
因为生气的男人责备羞耻
his old boss for not having a job right
他的老板因没有 正确的工作
now
现在
the third man thinks he and his wife
第三个人认为他和他的妻子
would be okay if she just spent way less
如果她只是少花钱就没关系
money and number four fears that his
钱和四号担心他的
wife no longer respects him as a man on
妻子不再尊重他作为一个男人
top of that two of the four have sought
这四个中的两个 人中最重要的是 寻求
medication so that they can feel better
用药让他们感觉更好
and a different two
和不同的两个
each spend more than six hours a day
每人每天花费超过六个小时
playing video games and only one of the
玩视频游戏，只有的一个
four knows the Bible must have the
四知道圣经必须有
solution to his problems and wants to
解决他的问题，并希望
hear about it
听到它
so what can we learn from this we should
那么我们应该从中学到什么呢？
consider each person individually gather
考虑每个人单独聚集
good data don't assume that the
好的数据不要假设了
counseling is like what it would be like
咨询就像它会是什么样的
for you if you didn't have a job find
如果你找不到工作的话
out what it's like for him to not have a
他没有一个像是什么样的
job and then gather that data at each
工作，然后收集每个数据
level each of the levels we've seen here
平衡我们在这里看到的每个级别
so that you really understand the
所以你真的明白了
problems completely then counsel from
问题完全然后劝告
Scripture at each level help the person
每个级别的经文都有助于此人
see how the Scriptures apply to each of
看看圣经如何适用于每一个
those levels of their worry beginning
他们担心的那些程度开始了
with the core issue well let's consider
我们考虑核心问题
the basic truths of fear or worry the
恐惧或担心的基本事实
Bible does have solutions to every
圣经确实有每一个解决方案
Christians fear or worry and this is
基督徒害怕或担心，这是
true because 2nd Timothy 3:16 and 17
是的，因为提摩太后书3:16和17
says that the scriptures are adequate
说经文是足够的
for every good work so that includes
对于每一项好工作，包括
dealing with fear or worry whether that
处理恐惧或担心是否那样
fear or worry is inside of our own soul
恐惧或忧虑是在我们自己的灵魂里面
or the souls of those we counsel and
或者我们劝告和帮助的人的灵魂
disciple well the first great truth that
门徒那是第一个伟大的真理
we're gonna look at is Hebrews 13 5 and
我们要看的是希伯来书135和
6 he himself has said I will never
6他自己说我永远不会
desert you nor will I ever forsake you
抛弃你，我也不会抛弃你
so that we confidently say the Lord is
所以我们自信地说主是
my helper I will not be afraid that
我的帮手我不会害怕的
sounds like the solution to fear and
听起来像恐惧和解决方案
then he even goes further he says what
然后他甚至走得更远，他说什么
shall man do to me
男人应该对我做
the lack of fear because the Lord is my
因为主是我的，所以没有恐惧
helper includes the fear of men so the
帮助者包括对男人的恐惧
rhetorical question implies that the
修辞问题意味着
worst another man can do to a Christian
另一个人可以对基督徒做的最坏的事情
is not worthy of fear in light of God's
根据上帝的说法，不值得害怕
faithfulness to that believer
对那个信徒的忠诚
well what can man do to us they can sin
还有什么人能把我们，他们可以犯罪
against us they can physically hurt us
对我们来说，他们可以伤害我们
they can even kill us but according to
他们甚至可以杀死我们，但根据
this passage if God is my God because he
如果上帝是我的上帝，那是因为他
will enable me to endure
会让我忍受
then I will emulate Jesus Christ and not
然后我会效仿耶稣基督而不是
fear man
害怕男人
even if I'm suffering for doing right
即使我因为做得正确而受苦
1st Corinthians 10:13 tells us that God
哥林多前书10:13告诉我们上帝
will not let us be tempted beyond what
不会让我们被诱惑超越什么
we're able and 1st Peter 2 18 to 25
我们能够和第一个彼得218到25
shows Jesus example of suffering for
显示了耶稣受苦的榜样
doing right and tells us to follow it
做得对，告诉我们要遵循它
point to Galatians 1:10 this is about
指向加拉太书1:10 这是关于
fearing God versus fearing men look how
害怕上帝与害怕男人一样
Paul puts these two as the opposite ends
保罗把这两个作为相反的目的
of the spectrum
光谱
he says for am I now seeking the favor
他说， 对上午我现在正在寻求青睐
of men or of God or am I still striving
不管是男人还是上帝还是我还在努力
to please men if I were still striving
如果我还在努力 ，请取悦男人
to please men I would not be a
为了取悦男人我不会是一个
bondservant of Christ so he has fearing
基督的仆人所以他害怕
man on one end of the scale and fearing
男人在规模和恐惧的一端
God on the other end of the scale
上帝在规模的另一端
pleasing man over there pleasing God
令人愉快的人在那里取悦上帝
over here
在这里
polar opposites if I apply this to my
如果我把它应用到我的身上，那就是两极
life I will come to the conclusion that
生活我会得出结论
if I care most about what people think
如果我最关心人们的想法
about me then I'm not doing what I'm
关于我然后我不做我的事
doing for the purpose of God's glory
为了上帝的荣耀而做
it's been said whatever someone loves
无论有人喜欢什么，都会说
the most is what they fear the most I
他们最害怕的是我
think there's a lot to that if I love
认为有很多，如果我爱
the approval of men the most then that's
男人的认可最多的是那个
what I want the most and then that's
我最想要的是那个
what I'm the most afraid of when I don't
当我不这样做时，我最害怕的是什么
have it if I love God the most I want to
如果我爱上帝，我就会拥有它
please him and bring him glory the most
请他，最让他荣耀
and serve him and so I'm going to be
为他服务，所以我会成为
fine because I can do that every day
很好，因为我每天都 可以这样做
what the circumstances are in many
许多情况都是如此
counseling cases the core change really
咨询案例真正的核心变化
is the counsel least choice to change
是改变的最佳选择
from either wanting approval from
从要么得到批准
themselves or someone else to seeking
他们自己或其他人寻求
God's glory in the same circumstances
在同样的情况下，上帝的荣耀
John 16:33 Jesus concludes the Upper
约翰福音16:33耶稣结束了上层
Room discourse with these final words he
房间话语与这些最后的话，他
says these things I have spoken to you
说我告诉你的这些事情
that in me you may have peace in the
在我身上你可能有平安
world you have tribulation but take
世界， 你有苦难，但采取
courage I have overcome the world the
我已经战胜了世界的勇气
counseling room is the perfect setting
咨询室是完美的环境
to come alongside the worrying Christian
与令人担忧的基督徒并肩作战
and teach them this important aspect of
并教导他们这个重要方面
their union with Christ because the
因为他们与基督联合
counsel II is in Christ and because the
律师二是在基督里，因为
Christ is in the counsel Li that
基督在律师李中
Christian can take courage because
基督徒可以采取勇气，因为
Christ overcame the world in the face of
基督面对世界克服了世界
any difficulty in their life today so
今天生活中有任何困难
this courage because Jesus Christ
这种勇气，因为耶稣基督
overcame the world is another solution
克服世界是另一种解决方案
to many types of worry and fear you
对许多类型的担心和恐惧你
might say to the council II something
可以说，以议会 II东西
like this the world is a tough place
像这样，世界是一个艰难的地方
counsel II but you are in Christ
律师二，但你在基督里
according to Romans 6:11 and according
根据罗马6:11，并根据
to Galatians 2:20 Christ is in you
加拉太书2:20基督在你里面
therefore because Jesus Christ overcame
因为耶稣基督得胜了
every temptation and you are Christ's
每一个诱惑，你都是基督的
you have great hope you can stand in
你有很大的希望，你可以忍受
against this temptation and overcome it
反对这种诱惑并克服它
you can have courage in the midst of the
你可以在中间获得勇气
difficult circumstances
困难的情况
so we encourage our counsel EES to take
所以我们鼓励我们的建议EES采取
courage well it has been such a great
勇气，它是如此伟大
pleasure over the years to have sat in
多年来一直享受的乐趣
my office or my house with many people
我的办公室或我的房子有很多人
who have had huge worries and fears and
谁都有过巨大的恐惧和忧虑，并
to see that these truths of the word as
看到这个词的真相如此
they memorize these truths as they
他们记住这些真理
dwelled on them as they chose to believe
当他们选择相信时，他们就会痴迷于他们
them and live by them were able to move
他们和他们的生活能够移动
from fear and worry to courage in Jesus
从恐惧和忧虑到耶稣的勇气
Christ and I'm confident that God will
基督和我相信上帝会
be able to use the word to strengthen
能够使用这个词加强
people in your lives as well
你生活中的人也是如此
let's take a look at first John 4:18 it
让我们先来看看约翰福音4:18 吧
tells us there is no fear in love but
告诉我们有爱里没有惧怕 ，但
perfect love casts out fear for many who
完美的爱情为许多人带来了恐惧
fear or worry a study of God's love
害怕或担心研究上帝的爱
results in hope when the counsel he
结果希望当他的律师
realizes that God's love is the only
意识到上帝的爱是唯一的
trustworthy love to be found then he or
值得信赖的爱， 然后他或他
she may also realize that to love God
她也可能意识到要爱上帝
above self also eliminates fear perfect
以上自我也消除了恐惧的完美
love casts out fear and next Hebrews 12
爱消除了恐惧和下一个希伯来书12
verses 1 through 3 it says this
它说这是第1节到第3节
therefore since we have so great a cloud
因为我们有这么大的云
of witnesses surrounding us let us also
我们周围的证人也让我们
lay aside every encumbrance and the sin
放下每一个负担和罪恶
which so easily entangles us and let us
这很容易缠绕我们，让我们
run with endurance the race that is set
与耐力一起运行所设定的比赛
before us fixing our eyes on Jesus the
在我们盯着耶稣之前
author and perfecter of faith who for
作者和信仰的完美者
the joy set before him endured the cross
他面前的欢乐忍受了十字架
despising the shame and he has sat down
鄙视羞耻，他坐了下来
at the right hand of God for consider
在上帝的右边考虑
him who endured such hostility by
他经历过这样的敌意
sinners against himself so that you may
罪人反对自己， 以便你可以
not grow weary and lose heart
不要厌倦而且会失去信心
the council Lee who fears or worries
担心或担心的理事会李
does often lose heart often that's why
的确常常失去心脏往往这就是为什么
they're coming to you
他们来找你
they've lost heart they've given up they
他们失去了心，他们已经放弃了
have no hope but according to Hebrews
根据希伯来书的说法，没有希望
12:1 through 3 by fixing their eyes on
12：1到3通过固定眼睛
Jesus Christ and considering him the
耶稣基督并考虑他
result will be they will not grow weary
结果将是他们不会厌倦
and they will not lose heart this is one
他们不会因为这一个而失去信心
of those passages that tells us the bold
那些告诉我们大胆的段落
effect of consideration and living by
考虑和生活的影响
what Jesus Christ did on the cross in a
耶稣基督在十字架上做了什么
practical way for our lives there was a
我们生活的实际方式 有一个
woman who came to our church for help
来到我们教会寻求帮助的女人
and she feared losing her son she came
她害怕失去她的儿子，她来了
for Biblical counseling her husband had
对于她丈夫的圣经辅导
remarried a young attractive woman and
再婚一个年轻有魅力的女人和
so this woman had her six-year-old on
所以这个女人已经六岁了
alternating weeks the other couple her
另一对夫妇互相交替
husband and the new wife often
丈夫和新婚妻子经常
criticized our counsel Lee - her son -
批评我们的律师李 - 她的儿子 -
old no money
老没钱
no fun that's what they'd say and they
没有乐趣，这就是他们所说的和他们
tried to get full custody so Sharon
沙龙试图完全保管
feared that her son would prefer the two
担心她的儿子更喜欢这两个
of them over her she also feared that
他们也担心她
her son would never come to Christ
她的儿子永远不会来到基督面前
because he would believe all the things
因为他会相信所有的事情
they said about her and they would that
他们谈到了她，他们就是这样
he would end up not respecting her or
他最终不会尊重她或
listening to her about anything
听她说什么
including the gospel well during
在此期间包括福音
counseling
辅导服务
Sharon memorized Hebrews 12:1 through 3
沙龙以12：1到3记住了希伯来书
and she lived by it she focused on
和她住它所她专注于
honoring God by enduring by trusting him
通过信任他来忍受尊重上帝
by emulating Christ and not fearing any
通过模仿基督而不是害怕任何人
more she developed a habit of measuring
她养成了更多的测量习惯
each day by how well she honored God
每一天她都尊重上帝
both on the days that Chad was with her
乍得和她在一起的日子
and during the
并期间
that he was at his dad's she had cards
他在他爸爸那里她有卡片
with scriptures from the hope from God's
来自上帝希望的经文
Word booklet in every room so she was
在每间客房字的小册子让她
never far away from these promises of
从来没有远离这些承诺
hope she memorized most of them and by
希望她能够记住他们中的大多数人
God's grace she trusted him and she
上帝的恩典她信任他和她
honored him greatly in really difficult
在非常困难的情况下非常尊敬他
circumstances she changed from a woman
她改变了一个女人的情况
who in the first five sessions was
谁在前五个会议上
frequently crying fearful and extremely
经常哭得很恐惧和极度
tentative during the times that she met
在她遇到的时候试探性的
with our female counselor and myself
和我们的女顾问和我一起
into a courageous and fearless servant
成为一个勇敢无畏的仆人
of Jesus Christ and how did this happen
耶稣基督，这是怎么发生的
it happened through her memorizing the
它发生在她背诵的时候
Word of God
上帝的话语
believing the Word of God and viewing
相信上帝的话语和观看
her circumstances accordingly so she
因此，她的情况如此
taught and trained her son from God's
从上帝那里教导和训练她的儿子
Word and she refused to criticize the
Word和她拒绝批评
other parents
其他的父母
well it's seven Chad told her that he
好吧，七乍得告诉她，他
appreciated her love and how she said
感谢她的爱和她说的话
what was true even when he did what was
甚至当他做了什么是真的 什么
wrong that was different than the other
与另一个不同的错误
house and then he began asking her
房子，然后他开始问她
questions about God by God's grace had
上帝的恩典有关于上帝的问题
eight he chose to believe in the gospel
八，他选择相信福音
and repent of sin Chad was saved at the
并且忏悔罪乍得被拯救了
age of eight at ten still spending
十岁时仍然有八岁
alternating weeks at each house he chose
在他选择的每个房子交替周
to communicate the gospel to his dad and
把福音传给他父亲和
his stepmom by God's grace
他的继母是上帝的恩典
Sharon continued as this strong faithful
沙龙继续作为这个坚强的信徒
woman and an excellent mother well the
女人和一位出色的母亲
point of the story is there is no
故事的重点是没有
guarantee of a child salvation but there
保证儿童得救，但在那里
is an absolute guarantee that God's Word
是神的话语的绝对保证
has the solution for every Christians
为每一位基督徒提供解决方案
worry and fear no matter how severe
无论多么严重 ，都要担心和担心
speaking of hope from God's Word you got
从上帝的话语中得到希望
this booklet from our church it has 15
我们教会的这本小册子有15本
scriptures with great promises of hope
有很大希望的经文
in it it's been an effective resource
在它里面它是一种有效的资源
for people that we've counseled for the
对于那些我们劝告过的人
last 14 years and I hope it'll be useful
过去14年，我希望它会有用
in your ministry as well so many people
在你的事工以及许多人
in fact think of think of people who
其实想思的人谁
have come to you for counseling how many
来找你咨询有多少人
of them had strong hope in God's Word
他们对上帝的话语寄予厚望
the day they came for help it's a low
他们来寻求帮助的那天很低
number it really is so aside from the
这个数字真的是这样的
counseling regarding the specific
关于具体的咨询
problem just helping them start thinking
只是帮助他们开始思考的问题
in terms of these are promises from God
就这些而言，是来自上帝的应许
to you Christian they're true and
给你基督徒他们是真实的
answering those questions about well if
回答那些关于好的问题
I believe this is true what will I think
我相信这是真的，我会怎么想
about my circumstances well let's take a
关于我的情况，让我们采取一个
look at the four components to worry or
看看要担心的四个组件或
to fear or worry before we break down
恐惧或担心 ，我们打破 之前
the presenting problems the underlying
提出问题的根本原因
fear the idle and the lies about the
害怕闲散和谎言
idle
闲
I just like to mention something about
我只想提一下
fear in most cases fears are not the
恐惧在大多数情况下恐惧不是
intentional desire of the one who has
有一个人的故意欲望
them so how did this person end up with
他们这个人最终是怎么做到的
these big fears or worries usually it
通常是这些大恐惧或担忧
starts as a reaction to circumstances
从对环境的反应开始
the adversity that they're under reveals
他们所处的逆境揭示了
the idol that maybe they didn't even
可能他们甚至没有的偶像
realize they had or realize how big it
意识到他们已经或意识到它有多大
was but the adversity opens the door and
是，但逆境打开门，
they now are dealing with that and so
他们现在正在处理这个问题
the fears are connected to the idol and
恐惧连接到偶像，
the reason they are afraid or worrying
他们害怕或担心的原因
is because there's this thing whatever
是因为有什么东西
it is other than God that they want so
他们想要的不仅仅是上帝
much and now they're afraid they're not
很多，现在他们害怕他们不是
going to get it or they have it and
得到它或他们拥有它
they're afraid they're going to lose it
他们担心他们会失去它
so the difficult circumstances turn on
所以困难的情况开启了
the light in that room that has the idol
那个有偶像的房间里的灯
in it but when the person comes to you
在它，但当人来找你
they don't tell you that they
他们没有告诉你他们
intentionally choose to fear because
故意选择恐惧，因为
they want that all they know is
他们想要他们所知道的一切
something happened and now I'm worried
事情发生了，现在我很担心
an event occurred in my life and now I'm
我生命中发生了一件事，现在我
afraid and I don't know what to do
害怕，我不知道该怎么办
because this is the case it's so
因为情况确实如此
important for us to approach the
对我们来说很重要
counselee with care and with patience
小心和耐心 counselee
and with love work to the core issue and
并以爱为核心问题而努力
then provide the biblical solution to
然后提供圣经的解决方案
the idol but work with the council leave
偶像，但与理事会一起离开
with that care and understanding and
有了这种关心和理解
christ-like love alright let's take a
基督般的爱， 好吧，让我们采取一个
look at these four components of fear or
看看恐惧或这四个组成部分
worry in detail first the presenting
先详细介绍一下
problem as we go through these things I
我们经历这些事情的问题我
ask you to pay attention to how I'm
请你注意我是如何
using the words of some and may
使用一些和可能的话
I'm not teaching that everyone with
我不是教人人有
these presenting problems fears or
这些提出的问题恐惧或
worries I'm saying that some people with
担心我说的是有些人
these presenting problems may have fears
这些提出的问题可能会引起恐慌
or worries so there's our disclaimer
或担心所以我们的免责声明
okay
好的
now let's think about these in a little
现在让我们稍微考虑一下这些
bit of detail often the presenting
一点点细节经常呈现
problem of the counselee is really in
该counselee的问题是真的
effect rather than the cause these
效果而不是原因
things they see as the problem but if
他们认为是问题但是如果
this person has a significant issue with
这个人有一个重大问题
worry or fear often these are the
经常担心或害怕这些是
effects of the worry or the fear but
担心或恐惧的影响但是
they don't know that when they come to
当他们来时，他们不知道
talk to you for example panic attacks
和你谈谈例如惊恐发作
when a person has what is called a panic
当一个人有所谓的恐慌
attack a recognized term in our culture
攻击我们文化中的公认术语
they have intense fear along with some
他们有一些强烈的恐惧
of these symptoms accelerated heart rate
这些症状加速了心率
trembling shaking shortness of breath
颤抖着喘不过气来
chest pain dizziness fear of losing
胸痛头晕怕失去
control or fear of going crazy fear of
控制或害怕去疯狂的恐惧
dying or numbness but then when they go
死亡或麻木，但他们去的时候
to the hospital the doctors can't find
去医院的医生找不到
anything physically wrong panic attacks
任何身体错误的惊恐发作
are connected to a particular intense
与特定的激烈相关
fear our counselors who have sought help
害怕寻求帮助的顾问
do to panic attacks have found that when
做惊恐发作的时候发现了
their fears were diminished due to trust
由于信任，他们的恐惧减少了
and obedience to the scriptures the
和服从圣经的
panic attacks ceased what about anorexia
恐慌发作停止了厌食症
or bulimia many teen girls who develop
或贪食症许多青少年女孩的发展
what the world calls anorexia or bulimia
世界上所谓的厌食症或贪食症
had as the origin of their problem and
有他们问题的起源和
inordinate fear this may be the fear of
过度恐惧这可能是恐惧
never being popular never being loved
永远不受欢迎永远不被爱
not being in control of the family or
不控制家庭或
not being able to succeed at everything
无法在一切事物上取得成功
multiple personalities how does that
多重性格怎么样？
happen
发生
the brain may invent different
大脑可能发明不同
identities when fears are so great that
当恐惧如此之大时的身份
the person believes they are unable to
该人认为他们无法做到
cope laziness some council ease come to
应对懒惰一些委员会的轻松来
us telling us that they have a lack of
我们告诉我们他们缺乏
motivation to work in many cases that is
在许多情况下工作的动力是
an effect caused by fear such as fear of
由恐惧引起的影响
failure also obsessive-compulsive many
失败也强迫许多人
people who alternate between the manic
人谁狂躁之间交替
and depressive states are driven by fear
和抑郁的状态是由恐惧驱动的
in both post-traumatic stress disorder
在两种创伤后应激障碍中
when someone has been sinned against
有人犯了罪
severely or suffered through traumatic
严重或遭受创伤
circumstances signs of stress may be
情节可能是压力的迹象
present this is generally not caused by
目前这通常不是由
the person who has suffered but is a
遭受苦难的人却是
reaction to extreme and difficult
对极端和困难的反应
circumstances but the promises of
但环境的承诺
Scripture regarding both trials and
关于审判和审判的经文
God's care are vital for these fellow
上帝的关心对这些人来说至关重要
believers and can help them through what
信徒，可以帮助他们通过什么
about lack of into intimacy with your
关于缺乏与你的亲密关系
spouse well some men and women who fear
配偶一些恐惧的男人和女人
rejection or worry about losing control
拒绝或担心失去控制
in the marital relationship may refuse
在婚姻关系中可能会拒绝
intimacy with their spouse if that's the
与他们的配偶亲密， 如果那是
case the problem is not sexual but is
这个问题不是性问题而是
fear or worry related also some people
有些人也担心或担心
have substance induced anxiety in other
在其他方面有物质引起的焦虑
words the cause of their worry or fear
说出他们担心或恐惧的原因
is completely physical how do we figure
是完全物理的我们如何计算
that out well we just have them go to a
说出来很好，我们只是让他们去
medical doctor and have physical tests
医生并进行身体检查
so if the doctor finds out it's due
所以，如果医生发现它是应该的
to an extreme intake of caffeine or if
到极度摄入咖啡因或是否
the doctor realizes that they're taking
医生意识到他们正在服用
these other prescription medications and
这些其他处方药和
one of the side effects of two of those
其中两个的副作用之一
three can be fear or worry then we
我们三个可能是恐惧或担心
realize that the cause of the fear or
意识到恐惧的原因还是
worry may be physical overeating some
担心可能是身体暴饮暴食
people eat more than is healthy in an
人吃的比在是健康的
attempt to shift their focus from their
试图将注意力从他们的转移
worries or fears lack of sleep similar
担心或担心睡眠不足相似
some people find it difficult to sleep
有些人觉得很难入睡
because they think so much about the
因为他们对此非常重视
things they are worried about or fearful
他们担心或害怕的事情
of and working too much others choose to
其他人选择和工作太多
work many extra hours to avoid the fears
多工作几个小时以避免恐惧
and worries at home so there are four
在家里担心所以有四个
components to fear and worry one is the
成分让人担心和担心
presenting problems the next one is the
提出问题的下一个是
underlying fear in these actual examples
在这些实际例子中潜在的恐惧
consider how the underlying fears
考虑潜在的恐惧
dictated the actions of the people for
决定了人民的行动
one person the fear was I must control
一个人害怕我必须控制
my spouse so they do not hurt me again
我的配偶所以他们不再伤害我了
and so the action was refusing to love
因此这一行动是拒绝爱情
selflessly or trust within the marriage
在婚姻中无私或信任
one person had this fear I can't live
一个人有这种恐惧，我无法生活
happily if my friends reject me and so
愉快，如果我的朋友拒绝我 等
what what were their actions that person
什么是他们的行为那个人
would sin to get the approval of the
会得到批准的罪
friends what about the person who whose
朋友那个人是谁
fear is I'm a victim of past sins
恐惧是我是过去罪恶的受害者
against me somebody who believes that
反对我的人相信这一点
that's true and they're fearful of it
这是真的，他们害怕它
well then that person lives in terror of
然后，那个人生活在恐怖之中
someone else sinning against them
别人犯了罪
because that's also going to cause some
因为那也会导致一些
serious and irreversible harm
严重和不可逆转的伤害
what about the person who fears I will
那个害怕我的人怎么样？
not achieve enough to think that my life
没有达到足以认为我的生活
mattered well what actions go with that
什么行动很重要
well this guy is working really hard but
好吧，这家伙真的很努力，但是
he's not doing his work hardly for the
他几乎没有做他的工作
Lord
主
the person who fears that they will be
害怕他们会成为的人
embarrassed and that will be the end of
尴尬，这将是结束
all their friendships that's probably
他们所有的友谊都可能
not a Christian who's communicating the
不是一个正在沟通的基督徒
gospel much what about the young single
福音很多年轻单身
guy who thinks no Christian girl will
认为没有基督徒女孩愿意的家伙
ever want to marry me the way I am well
我想以我的方式嫁给我
this is a guy who lies a lot when he's
这是一个在他的时候经常撒谎的人
around Christian girls and because he's
围绕基督徒女孩，因为他是
given up hope he also talks to
放弃希望他也会谈
non-christian girls online or maybe the
非基督教女孩在线或者也许是
female equivalent the the gal who's
女性相当于gal的人
single and she thinks I will not be thin
单身，她认为我不会瘦
enough to be liked by the guys that I
足以由人来喜欢我
would like to marry that girl probably
想或许那女孩结婚
spends a lot of time clothes shopping
花很多时间买衣服
and not much in ministry some people
有些人在事工上并不多
have this fear that if my marriage fails
有这种担心， 如果我的婚姻失败
that would be too overwhelming for me to
这对我来说太难以承受了
go on with normal life the person with
继续正常生活的人
that fear is depressed and then for the
那种恐惧是沮丧的，然后是为了
person whose fear that a physical
害怕身体的人
illness will become too difficult to
疾病会变得太难了
bear one person like that spent nine
忍受一个人花了九个人
hours a day on the internet trying to
小时在互联网上每天努力
find a cure one counseled he feared that
找到一个治疗方法，他担心他会这样做
they would not be strong enough to
他们不会强大到足以
really trust God and that person was
真的相信上帝而那个人是
terrified of hard times and the person
害怕困难时期和人
whether they're 12 or 50 who thinks dad
他们是12岁还是50岁，他们认为是爸爸
will think I'm a failure or
会认为我是失败或
mom will never love me it's worried
妈妈永远不会爱我，这让人很担心
about pretty much everything so we've
关于我们所做的几乎所有事情
considered the presenting problems we've
考虑到我们提出的问题
considered the underlying fears that are
考虑到潜在的担心是
part of each case of fear or worry what
每个案例的一部分恐惧或担心什么
about the idol the idol is the core of
关于偶像是偶像的核心
fear or worry to find out the I when you
害怕或担心在你找到我的时候
find out the idol then you know where
找出偶像然后你知道在哪里
change must occur occur the idol is the
必须发生变化才会发生偶像
thing that the person wants so much that
那个人想要的东西那么多
their whole fear or worry is based on if
他们整个恐惧或担心都是基于if
I don't get that my life will be a mess
我不明白我的生活会变得一团糟
or I have it now but if I lose it I will
或者我现在拥有它，但如果我失去它，我会
be destroyed so what is that thing in
被破坏所以那是什么东西
this person's life what is the idol what
这个人的生活是什么偶像是什么
is the thing that they want more than
是他们想要的东西
anything else the common idols that are
别的常见的偶像是
the root of fear or worry control being
恐惧或忧虑控制的根源
loved peace for some it's being the
对某些人来说，爱是和平的
parent of great kids for some it's money
对于一些有钱的孩子的父母来说
sometimes the reason they want money is
有时他们想要钱的原因是
for safety sometimes for pleasure
为了安全，有时为了愉快
sometimes for achievement and for some
有时是为了成就而对某些人来说
people the idol is revenge can you see
人们偶像是复仇你能看到吗？
how if somebody wanted any of those
怎么会有人想要这些呢？
things more than anything else including
最重要的事情包括
honoring God how that would result in
尊重上帝将如何导致
fear or worry if they thought they they
恐惧或担心，如果他们认为他们自己
couldn't ever get that or couldn't keep
无法得到或无法保持
that so we need to find out what the
所以我们需要找出什么
idol is because when a Christian desires
偶像是因为当基督徒渴望时
one of those things more than they
其中之一比他们更多
desire to obey God then they will sin to
他们愿意服从上帝然后他们会犯罪
get or keep the idol so we use homework
得到或保持偶像所以我们使用作业
assignments that are designed to cause
被设计任务造成
the counselee to a value
所述counselee的值
their motives by Scripture the last
他们的动机是最后的经文
component in fear or worry are these
恐惧或担忧的成分就是这些
lies about the idols usually the lies
关于偶像通常是谎言
that a person believes about the idol
一个人相信偶像
are more blatantly opposite of Scripture
更明显地反对圣经
than the idol itself and so when you
比偶像本身所以当你
find out what the person tells themself
找出这个人告诉自己的东西
every day in their pursuit of the idol
每天都在追求偶像
you're getting you're gaining very
你得到的非常好
important information for example well
例如重要信息，以及
this is too difficult so I just can't do
这太难了所以我就是做不到
right or God wants me to be happy he
对，或上帝希望我快乐他
wants me to have this idol one council
我希望我有这个偶像一个议会
he said I'm all alone and no one can
他说我一个人而且没人能
help me for some it's as simple as
帮助我一些简单的事情
believing that hard times are bad as
相信困难时期是坏
opposed to what James 1 says they're
与詹姆斯1所说的相反
actually good we should give thanks for
其实很好，我们应该给予感谢
them it's a high position because we
他们是高位，因为我们
have that opportunity to grow in faith
有机会在信仰中成长
and honor Christ and then there was this
并尊重基督然后有这个
one council II who wanted to control her
一个想要控制她的理事会II
life at 28 she was married to her high
生活在28，她嫁给了她的高
school sweetheart and had four children
学校的心上人，有四个孩子
both were Christians since she got
她得到的都是基督徒
married she completed two college
结婚她完成了两个大学
degrees and she was advancing in the
度，她在推进
corporate world she told us that she
企业界她告诉我们她
believed that if she was single she
相信如果她单身，她
could get an educated rich and
可以得到一个受过教育的富人和
better-looking husband she feared she
她害怕她的好看的丈夫
would hate her life if she didn't go for
如果她不去，她会恨她的生活
it and so she told us number five there
它告诉我们那里的第五号
she said quote it is a sin to divorce
她说这是离婚的罪
but afterward I will repent and then
但之后我会悔改然后
marry a better spouse she told herself
她告诉自己娶了一个更好的配偶
that lie so that she could continue to
那谎言让她可以继续
pursue her idol when you find out what
当你发现什么时，追求她的偶像
the lies are then you can
那么谎言就可以了
kill them with Scripture you can
你可以用圣经杀死他们
obliterate them with truth from God's
用上帝的真理抹杀他们
Word and when that happens the idol is
单词，当发生这种情况时， 偶像就是
exposed for what it is the opposition of
暴露于什么是反对派
the Living God that's helpful when we
活着的上帝，当我们有帮助时
get to that point with our Council Lee
与我们的李议会达成这一点
they see it all really clearly and
他们看到这一切真的很清楚，
they're in the best spot to respond to
他们是回应的最佳地点
God's Word all right please take a look
上帝的话可以请你看看
at page 67 this is a study by a Lisa
在第67页，这是 Lisa的 一项研究
Johnston that was crucial in a biblical
约翰斯顿在圣经中至关重要
counseling case involving fear the
咨询案涉及恐惧
council II was a single gal who had many
理事会II是一个有很多人的gal
intense fears and so this chart showed
强烈的恐惧，所以这张图表显示
that the fears were initiated by
恐惧是由...发起的
pressures or trials when difficult
压力或试验困难时
things happened then the fear was the
事情发生了然后恐惧就是了
fear began but then there was a choice
恐惧开始但随后有了选择
there was the choice to trust God's
有信任上帝的选择
promises and seek to honor him in the
承诺并设法尊重他
midst of adversity or to fear and and an
在逆境或恐惧之中
important thing in this is for her to
这件事的重点在于她
know that the biblical principle is that
我知道圣经原则就是这样
feelings follow the choice if she chose
如果她愿意，感情会跟随选择
to honor God she would be confident in
为了纪念上帝，她会有信心
the promises of God and be at peace if
如果，上帝的应许和平安
she chose to fear then the feelings of
她选择了那种恐惧感
fear would come and then the result of
恐惧会来，然后结果
the feelings was the outcome peace or
感情是结果还是和平
intense fear in that case and so on each
那种情况下的强烈恐惧等等
side we have the scriptures that endorse
我们有经文赞同
worshiping God and the and the
崇拜上帝和他们
principles about worshiping self and so
关于崇拜自我的原则等等
for each step going down the center it
从中心走下去的每一步
was always that choice worshiping God or
总是那种崇拜上帝的选择
worshiping self when this gal made a
当这个gal成为一个时，崇拜自我
habit pattern of worshiping God the
崇拜上帝的习惯模式
fears diminished
恐惧减少了
there are five keys to effectively
有效地有五个关键
counseling people who fear or worry
为恐惧或担心的人提供咨询
let's take a look at those number one
让我们来看看第一名
first John 3:16 love and lay down your
约翰一书3:16 爱和放下你的
life for this believer be committed to
这个信徒的生命将致力于
it it's a hard case it'll probably take
这是它可能会采取 强硬的情况下
a while there will be quite a few
一段时间会有不少
different layers to it but this is a
不同的层，但这是一个
person for whom Christ died they're in a
基督为之而死的人， 他们是在一个人
really difficult spot be thankful for
非常困难的地方要感恩
this opportunity to serve them and walk
这个机会为他们服务并走路
with them down this road no matter how
无论怎样 ，他们都沿着这条路走下去
long it is
很久了
second Colossians 3:12 offer compassion
第二个歌罗西书3:12提供同情心
kindness humility gentleness and
善良谦卑的温柔和温柔
patience if that's what you're fearful
耐心， 如果那是你的恐惧
or worrying counsel league gets from you
或令人担忧的律师联盟得到你
every time they see you that will help
每当他们看到你会有所帮助
them realize that the promises in God's
他们意识到上帝的应许
Word are true they'll know that you
言语是真的， 他们会知道你
believe it they'll know that you truly
相信它他们会真的知道你
love them that you're not like freaked
爱他们，你不喜欢吓坏了
out and leaving them because you know
因为你知道而离开他们
they're fearful and that will open the
他们害怕，这将打开
door to involvement and Trust and them
参与和信任的大门和他们
being able to both tell you the core
能够告诉你核心
issues and hear the truths of the word
问题和听到这个词的真相
of God in response another important
上帝在回应另一个重要的
factor in this is data gathering tools
因素是数据收集工具
Hebrews 4 12 and 13 teaches that the
希伯来书4章12和13教导说
Word of God can judge the thoughts and
上帝的话可以判断思想和
intentions of the heart having homework
有作业的心脏的意图
assignments that connect the counsel Lea
连接律师Lea的作业
with relevant scriptures where they're
他们有相关的经文
writing about how those truths relate to
写下这些真相如何相关
the idol the lies they tell themselves
偶像他们告诉自己的谎言
about the idol and the fear will put all
关于偶像和恐惧将把所有
of those things out there on the table
那些东西在桌子上
so you can discuss them it'll help you
所以你可以讨论它们会帮助你
understand their motives and be able to
了解他们的动机和能
communicate the Word of God in the most
最能传达神的话语
effective way questions during the
有效的方式问题
counseling session during the week in
本周的咨询会议
between when I meet with someone
在我遇到某人之间
I generally plan at least three
我一般计划至少三个
questions that I word very carefully to
我非常认真地提出的问题
gather more information I look through
收集我看穿更多信息
all the notes of the previous sessions
前几届会议的所有笔记
and I try to figure out what do I need
我试着找出我需要什么
to know most now to be able to counsel
现在最了解能够提供咨询
this person from God's Word and I found
这个人来自上帝的话，我找到了
that at least for me if I'm sitting
如果我坐着，至少对我而言
there and I have plenty of time to to
那里和我有足够的时间去
word and reword and think you know how
单词和reword，并认为你知道如何
can I say this exactly so that I'm
我可以说，这正是让我
asking the question I intend to ask I'm
问我打算问我的问题
getting the information that I need that
获取我需要的信息
seems to work much better than just
似乎比公正的工作要好得多
making up the questions as I go along
构成问题，因为我走
journals with Scripture take a look at
使用圣经的期刊看一看
page 79 I have a couple of these as
第79页我有几个这样的
samples for you I hope they'll be
样品给你我希望他们会
helpful for you in your ministry but
在你的事工中对你有帮助但是
page 79 is the fear journal there's
第79页是那里的恐惧期刊
there are scriptures that deal with fear
有经文可以解决恐惧问题
that are connected so I've got the
连接所以我得到了
counseling looking through a set of
咨询通过一组
those scriptures every day and then
每一天，然后将这些经文
they're giving me a play-by-play
他们给了我一个游戏
description of their biggest temptation
描述他们最大的诱惑
to fear that day what happened
害怕那天发生了什么
what truths about God addressed the
什么真理神讲话
temptation to fear what did they choose
害怕他们选择什么
to think about their fear and what
想想他们的恐惧和什么
feelings resulted from the choice that
这种感觉来自于选择
they made these are really helpful for
他们做这些都是非常有帮助
people because if you've got somebody
人，因为如果你有人
doing this seven days a week then pretty
这样每周七天 ，然后漂亮
soon at the moment that they realize I'm
很快，在他们意识到我的那一刻
tempted to be afraid they're starting to
他们害怕开始害怕
think about okay which scriptures apply
想想哪些经文适用
to this and then they realize I have a
对此，然后他们意识到我有一个
choice I can believe those truths from
选择我可以相信这些真理
God's Word and honor him here or I'd
上帝的话语在这里尊敬他，或者我
have to ignore those to go ahead with
必须忽略那些继续下去
this fear that's really helpful for them
这种担心对他们真的很有帮助
these are also great data gathering
这些也都是伟大的数据收集
tools because you you just you see what
工具，因为你只是你看到了什么
happens every single day at the crucial
每一天都发生在关键时刻
point in that day in your counselors
在那天指导你的辅导员
life there's also a list of good
生活中还有一个好的清单
resources at the end of this section and
在本节的最后资源和
please use those other effective
请使用其他有效的
information other information that's
信息其他信息
needed to counsel the person with fear
需要为恐惧的人提供咨询
or worry how do they they fear a man
或担心他们如何害怕男人
in virtually every case that involves
几乎在每种情况下都涉及到
fear or worry there's a component to it
担心或担心它有一个组成部分
that is fearing man it may not be the
所担心的人可能 不是
main thing but it's there find out what
但主要的是它找到了什么
it is and then I'll just analyze which
它是，然后我将分析哪个
which issues are caused and which are
哪些问题是由哪个引起的
effect so then we do the hard work of
效果，那么我们就做了艰苦的工作
assessing and analyzing all that data
评估和分析所有数据
with Scripture and then we confidently
用经文，然后我们自信
proclaim God's solution to the fear or
宣告上帝对恐惧或恐惧的解决方案
worry here are some practical aspects of
担心这里的一些实际问题
teaching the truth of God's Word to the
教导上帝圣言的真理
counselee who fears our worries develop
担心我们的忧虑发展的顾问
the habit of refuting the lies about the
驳斥有关谎言的习惯
idol with Scripture teach the counselee
偶像与圣经教导辅导员
to turn from the idol to honoring God
从偶像转向尊重上帝
help them see those as the two ends of
帮助他们将这些视为两端
that scale encourage them to live to
那种规模鼓励他们活着
please God not self or other people also
请上帝不要自己或其他人
we're exhorting them from the word to
我们从这个词劝他们
live to obey God rather than to control
活着服从上帝而不是控制
people or circumstances we encourage
我们鼓励的人或情况
them to take biblical courage to fear
他们采取圣经的勇气来恐惧
God not man to trust God's promises and
上帝不是人相信上帝的应许和
to understand and live in God's love I
了解和生活在上帝的爱中我
have three actual cases that I'd like to
有三个我想要的实际案例
tell you about that I hope will
告诉你 ，我希望会
encourage you just to see how these
鼓励你看看这些是怎样的
principles for counseling the person
咨询人的原则
with worry and fear work in real life
在现实生活中担忧和恐惧
and also just to rejoice together with
而且也只是为了欢欣鼓舞
me over how God's word is sufficient and
关于上帝的话是如何充分的
he changes lives through it in the first
他在第一次改变生活
case the presenting problem he was
他提出的问题
suspected of corporate theft at the
涉嫌企业被盗的
office the underlying fear I'm gonna
办公室潜在的恐惧我会
lose my job and go to prison the idol
失去工作，去监狱偶像
was work and esteem of co-workers were
为同事的工作和自尊是
his whole life the worst thing about
他一生中最糟糕的事情
being found guilty and going to prison
被判有罪并入狱
for him was what his coworker
对他来说就是他的同事
would think about it and so the lies
会去想它，所以谎言
that he told himself about the idol were
他告诉自己这个偶像
my life will be worthless if this
如果这样，我的生命将毫无价值
happens they probably already think I'm
发生他们可能已经认为我是
a loser and shame will follow me for the
一个失败者和耻辱会跟着我的
rest of my life well it took about three
我的余生好了大约需要三个人
weeks before this brother trusted me
在这位兄弟信任我的前几周
enough to tell me the whole problem he
足以告诉我他 的整个问题
had a fake problem he told me about and
有一个假的问题，他告诉我和
he told me at the end of that third week
他在第三周结束时告诉我
okay now I think I can trust you enough
好吧，现在我觉得我可以信任你了
here's what's actually going on the idol
这就是偶像的实际情况
and the wise of about the idol that he
关于他的偶像的聪明人
told himself all day
整天告诉自己
were really the core issue for him so in
对他来说真的是核心问题
this case Trust was built through honest
这种情况信托是通过诚实建立的
communication of the word and personal
传达这个词和个人
care that was really huge with this guy
对这个家伙来说真是太大了
when I met this guy he had not been in
当我遇到这个他没有去过的人时
the word much for many years but then
这个词很多年，但后来
when he did the homework of the daily
当他做了每日的作业
scripture study and application and the
经文研究与应用
journal that I gave him he began to view
我给他的期刊他开始观察
his trials biblically he came back to
他的审判以圣经的方式回来了
biblical thinking it was through God's
圣经的想法是通过上帝的
work and God's active use of the word in
工作和 神的积极使用这个词的
this guy's life that changed it all
这家伙的生活改变了这一切
around he realized the core of his sin
他意识到自己犯罪 的核心
and he repented when he changed he
当他改变他时他悔改了
changed from living for work and living
工作和生活从改变生活
for the people at work to living for God
为工作的人们为上帝而活
and he began living for God at work and
他开始在工作和生活中为上帝而活
away from work his fears went away he
远离工作，他的恐惧消失了
was no longer afraid he knew he was
不再害怕他知道他是谁
innocent he wasn't guilty of theft he
无辜的他没有犯盗窃罪
did lose his job he did not go to prison
确实失去了他的工作，他没有去监狱
but he wasn't crushed by the outcome and
但他并没有被结果压垮
so he honored God greatly during the 18
所以他在18岁期间大大尊敬上帝
months of unemployment and he's been
几个月的失业和他一直在
walking with God and involved in
与上帝同行并参与其中
ministry at his church in the many years
多年来他在教会的事工
since I was exciting number two the
因为我是令人振奋的数字两
presenting problem was anorexia for this
提出问题是厌食此
teenage gal the underlying fear was no
十几岁的孩子潜在的恐惧是没有的
one will ever
一个永远
me the idol was being loved by her peers
我的偶像被同龄人所爱
and the lies that she told herself and
和谎言，她告诉自己，
these were the lies that she told
这些是她告诉的谎言
herself starting from about the middle
她从大约中间开始
of her weight-loss getting all this
她的瘦身得到了这一切
positive attention makes life complete
积极关注使生活完整
if I gain any weight back I will lose
如果我恢复体重，我会输
all this great attention and attention
所有这些极大的关注和关注
from boys is more important than loving
男孩比爱更重要
God so here's the story she was 17 she
上帝，所以这就是她17岁的故事
was smart she was successful at
很聪明，她成功了
everything everything except being
除了存在之外的一切
popular at school and so she often cried
在学校很受欢迎， 所以她经常哭
herself to sleep thinking that she would
自己睡觉以为她愿意
never be asked to marry by anyone so
永远不会被要求任何人因此娶
that summer she went on a hardcore diet
那个夏天，她进行了核心饮食
and as the week's went by her life
随着她的生命一周过去了
changed she lost weight and pretty soon
改变了她很快就减肥了
even cool non-christian guys started
甚至很酷的非基督徒家伙也开始了
talking to her when we met her was three
我们见到她时跟她说话的是三个
months later and 47 more pounds lost
几个月后又减掉了47磅
after that she told us she remembered
之后，她告诉我们她记得
every single day of summer but she
夏天的每一天，但她
didn't remember any of the three months
不记得三个月中的任何一个
since during that time her pattern was
因为在那段时间她的模式是
she would get up early and run enough to
她会早起足够运行
burn all 600 calories that she had
燃烧她所有的600卡路里
consumed the prior day well she was a
她很早就消耗了前一天
celebrity at her school but she also one
在她的学校名人，但她也是一个
day collapsed because of the lack of
由于缺乏，一天崩溃了
nutrition during our time of eating
我们吃饭时的营养
together God used His Word to dispel
一起上帝用他的话语 打消
each of the lies about the idol it was
关于偶像的每一个谎言
crucial for her to realize the Bible
她认识圣经至关重要
says something about each of those lines
说了解每一条线
and when she realized that she she
当她意识到她的时候
changed so through the study of the word
通过对这个词的研究改变了
and her writing and the corresponding
和她的写作和相应的
journal and she wrote a lot she turned
期刊和她写了很多，她转过身来
from her idol to the purposes of loving
从她的偶像到爱的目的
God and maintaining her body in a
上帝和保持她的身体在一
healthy way for his glory such a joy to
健康的方式让他的荣耀如此快乐
see God work through his word in that
看到上帝在他的话语中起作用
girl's life
女孩的生活
final example panic attacks this
最后的例子惊恐发作了
person's fear was that they weren't
人的恐惧是他们不是
really saved because of some sin they
真的因为某些罪而得救了
had done a long time ago their Idol was
做了很久以前的偶像
they just wanted to know that they were
他们只是想知道他们是
in God's will
在上帝的旨意中
and the lies that this gal believed
和这个gal相信的谎言
about the idol was that she somehow left
关于偶像是她不知何故离开了
the the narrow paths of God's will
上帝旨意的狭隘道路
twelve years ago and she could never get
十二年前，她永远无法得到
back and so whenever her husband
背部等 ，每当她的丈夫
criticized her she's thought God is
批评她， 她认为上帝是
judging me because I left the past and
判断我，因为我离开了过去
she also believed that she had an
她还相信她有一个
undiscovered disease and that she would
未被发现的疾病， 她会
die a painful death so you see how
死得很痛， 所以你看怎么样
there's a few different fears mixed in
有一个在混合几个不同的恐惧
to this she was 33 she had come to
为此，她来了33岁
believe that she had married the wrong
相信她已经结婚了
man cliff wasn't the guy that she
男人悬崖不是她的那个人
thought he would be she had heard some
以为他会听到一些
inaccurate teaching about God's will in
关于上帝的旨意的不准确的教导
college and so she believed that when
大学所以她相信的时候
she was 20 she had departed from this
她20岁就离开了这个
narrow line and that she could never
狭窄的线条，她永远不会
find her way back she had had three
找到她回来的路， 她有三个
different panic attacks each time same
每次都有不同的惊恐发作
things thought she was having a heart
事情以为她有一颗心
attack thought she was going to die
袭击以为她会死
rushed to the emergency room by her
她被送往急诊室
husband everything was fine
老公一切都很好
no physical problems and her core fear
没有身体问题和她的核心恐惧
was that she might not even really be a
是她甚至可能不是真的
Christian because she had departed from
克里斯蒂安因为她离开了
God's will back then well so what were
那时候上帝会回来的
the key things you can probably guess
你可能猜到的关键事情
well first we we studied God's will in
首先，我们研究了上帝的旨意
detail with her we helped her understand
细节与她我们帮助她了解
the truth about God's will and that her
关于上帝的意志和她的真相
theory could not be true next we helped
接下来我们帮助理论不可能是真的
her realize how to biblically deal with
她意识到如何以圣经的方式处理
her husband's sin
她丈夫的罪
she chose to believe in obey God's Word
她选择相信顺从上帝的话语
on both matters for her also it was
在这两件事上对她来说也是如此
really huge she memorized all the
真的很大，她背诵了所有的
scriptures and hope from God's Word and
从上帝的话语和经文中得到经文和希望
during the nights when she was awake and
在她清醒的夜晚
struggling to sleep and the temptation
挣扎着睡觉和诱惑
was all the fears she would refute those
所有人都担心她会反驳这些人
fears with the truth of God's Word
害怕上帝话语的真理
it was exciting as time went by through
随着时间的流逝，这是令人兴奋的
the spiritual disciplines regular time
精神纪律定期
in the word and prayer going to church
在这个词和祈祷去教堂
being involved in ministry
参与事工
she changed further she never had
她变得更加前所未有
another panic attack and in the time
另一次惊恐发作和时间
since she has been a strong mature
因为她已经成熟了
Christian woman God's Word is sufficient
基督徒女神上帝的话就足够了
for the problems of worry and fear
对于担心和恐惧的问题
I hope these practical aspects of
我希望这些实际方面
counseling the person who fears or
咨询恐惧或恐惧的人
worries will be helpful to you I say may
我可以说，担心会对你有所帮助
God bless your ministry to people who
上帝保佑你的事的人谁
fear or worry
害怕或担心